{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "What _________ is the matter with him?",
      "a": "on earth",
      "b": "in world",
      "c": "does",
      "d": "more",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- On earth \n- In the world",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tom, why did you come so early for lunch today? \"I thought the bell ___\"",
      "a": "already had rung",
      "b": "has already rung",
      "c": "had already rung",
      "d": "already rang",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Have/has/had + already + pp",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Michael has lived in Vietnam for ten years. \"Yes, but he _________ doesn't understand Vietnamese.\"",
      "a": "yet",
      "b": "still",
      "c": "al ready",
      "d": "any more",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Still: usually comes before any negative word or before \"do not\"",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are the days getting colder? \" ___ \"",
      "a": "Yes, it is",
      "b": "No, it isn't",
      "c": "Yes, they are",
      "d": "No, they don't",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- The days (plural) -&gt; they are",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have to leave now. \"Well, I hope we see each other again ___.\"",
      "a": "before many days",
      "b": "before some time",
      "c": "in few days",
      "d": "before long",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Before long = soon\n- In a few days",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jackson put the plants ___ the show window.",
      "a": "near",
      "b": "close",
      "c": "nearly",
      "d": "next",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- near = only a short distance from a person or thing\n- close to \n- next to",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "You _________ go out lest it should rain.",
      "a": "had not better",
      "b": "had better not",
      "c": "not had better",
      "d": "better had not",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Had better not",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Susie arrived here a week ___, and has been here ever ___.",
      "a": "before, ago",
      "b": "before, since",
      "c": "ago, before",
      "d": "ago, since",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- ago, since\n- past tense: ago\n- present perfect tense: since",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kennedy did not get up until nine that morning and he arrived at the meeting ___.",
      "a": "too late much",
      "b": "too much late",
      "c": "much too late",
      "d": "late too much",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- much too + adjective. Ex: much too late/big/old etc\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Winnie married ___ she graduated from college.",
      "a": "soon",
      "b": "immediately",
      "c": "early",
      "d": "fast",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Without delay, right away (syn at once)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "5"
    }
  ]
}